<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Woof App</string>
    <string name="dog_name_1">Koda</string>
    <string name="dog_name_2">Lola</string>
    <string name="dog_name_3">Frankie</string>
    <string name="dog_name_4">Nox</string>
    <string name="dog_name_5">Faye</string>
    <string name="dog_name_6">Bella</string>
    <string name="dog_name_7">Moana</string>
    <string name="dog_name_8">Tzeitel</string>
    <string name="dog_name_9">Leroy</string>
    <string name="dog_description_1">Eating treats on the terrace</string>
    <string name="dog_description_2">Barking at Daddy</string>
    <string name="dog_description_3">Stealing socks</string>
    <string name="dog_description_4">Meeting new animals</string>
    <string name="dog_description_5">Digging in the garden</string>
    <string name="dog_description_6">Chasing sea foam</string>
    <string name="dog_description_7">Bothering her paw-rents</string>
    <string name="dog_description_8">Sunbathing</string>
    <string name="dog_description_9">Sleeping in dangerous places</string>
    <string name="about">About:</string>
    <string name="years_old">%d years old</string>
    <string name="expand_button_content_description">See more or less information about a dog.</string>
    <string name="description_1">Koda enjoys spending time outdoors, especially indulging in treats on the terrace. This little one loves snacking while enjoying the fresh air</string>
    <string name="description_2">Despite her age, Lola still has a lot of energy, especially when it comes to barking at Daddy. She’s always on alert and ready to make her presence known!</string>
    <string name="description_3">Frankie has a mischievous streak, stealing socks and making everyone chase him around. He keeps things lively with his playful antics.</string>
    <string name="description_4">Nox loves meeting new animals, making every encounter an exciting adventure. His curiosity keeps him engaged and friendly towards new friends.</string>
    <string name="description_5">Faye is a natural digger, spending her time happily working in the garden. She enjoys creating her own little spots and exploring the outdoors.</string>
    <string name="description_6">Even in her golden years, Bella still loves chasing sea foam along the beach, enjoying the freedom and joy of the seaside.</string>
    <string name="description_7">Moana is known for bothering her paw-rents, always demanding attention and making sure shes the center of the action.</string>
    <string name="description_8">Tzeitel loves to soak up the sun and relax, often found sunbathing and enjoying the warmth and peace.</string>
    <string name="description_9">Leroy is an adventurous sleeper, often choosing dangerous or unusual spots for his naps. His bold choices keep his owners on their toes!</string>
    <string name="id_1">1</string>
    <string name="id_2">2</string>
    <string name="id_3">3</string>
    <string name="id_4">4</string>
    <string name="id_5">5</string>
    <string name="id_6">6</string>
    <string name="id_7">7</string>
    <string name="id_8">8</string>
    <string name="id_9">9</string>
</resources>